Gabriel Maia

FullStack Developer

Location: Manaus, Amazonas, Brazil| Phone: +55 92 992795598 | Email:

gribeiromaia736@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabriel-maia-dev

SUMMARY

FullStack developer with more than 3 years of experience in international products and consultancy for companies. Proven ability to use Node, React.js, Next.js, Angular, AWS Services, GCP, Docker technologies for maintenance and Web features. But also knowledge in Mobile technologies and data analysis. And also alongside agile methodology tools such as Scrum, Kanban and Jira

SKILLS

Proficient: Angular, React.js, Node, Next.js, Express, Nest.js, Fastify, Javascript, Typescript, Sequelize

Intermediate: Aws, Python, MongoDb, Java, Redis

Beginner: C#, .Net, C++, Kubernetes

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Data Analyst

Converge Tech, Manaus, BR

05/2022 to 12/2022

Core Responsibilities:

- Created new bank models and improvements for Customers
- Automated the process of evaluating some essential data for forming result graphs with scripts
- Carrying out ETL processes

Key Technologies and Tools: Python, NumPy, Pandas, TensorFlow, MySQL, SQLAlchemy, Requests

FullStack Developer Intern

Sidia - Samsung, Manaus, BR

12/2022 to 06/2023

Core Responsibilities:

- Creation of new features and bug fixes for existing products
- Participation in meetings with clients and in the advancement of new projects
- Application development and project presentation
- Conducting POC's and testing to implement features

Key Technologies and Tools: React is, React Native, Node, Express, Prisma, Zod, Firebase, MySQL

FullStack Developer

Eldorado Institute - Motorola, BR – Remote

07/2023 until Now

Core Responsibilities:

- Maintenance of a Motorola product, fixing bugs and implementing new features
- Market research and evaluation of new features to be implemented together with the client
- Mentoring interns to ensure their best use and development
- Testing and improvements to the AWS Cloud infrastructure of products

• Python script implementation for AWS Glue Job features

Key Technologies and Tools: Angular, PrimeNg, Node, Express, Sequelize, Python, Docker, AWS Services

EDUCATION

Systems Analysis and Development

Estácio University's, Amazon, Brasil

02/2022 to 08/2024

• Relevant coursework: Business and Inteligence.

CERTIFICATES/COURSES

Android Enterprise Expert, Android AWS Cloud Practicioner, Amazon Web Services BootCamp Microservices, Udemy

March/2024 July/2024 November/2024

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Native

English: B2, and studying and training speaking and listening

Spanish: B2